<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jack Higgins</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jack Higgins</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/customer_comms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/customer_comms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;dns-record-change-guide&#34;&gt;DNS record change guide&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where to view this portfolio piece: on this page.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As mentioned in &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/customer_responses/&#34;&gt;Technical support responses&lt;/a&gt;, I currently work in Support at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fastmail.com/&#34;&gt;Fastmail&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of customers use Fastmail to host one or more simple static websites. Due to some changes to Fastmail&amp;rsquo;s internal networks, the IP addresses that users&amp;rsquo; websites were hosted on were scheduled for change. We could make these changes automatically for customers hosting their DNS at Fastmail, but we needed those who were not to manually update DNS records at their host.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/customer_responses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/customer_responses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;technical-support-responses&#34;&gt;Technical support responses&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where to view this portfolio piece: on this page.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I currently work as a customer support technician at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fastmail.com/&#34;&gt;Fastmail&lt;/a&gt;, an Australian email service provider. In this role, I&amp;rsquo;m responsible for guiding customers through technical configuration challenges each and every day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many of the challenges our customers face involve incredibly complex technical systems, including DNS and email authentication protocols.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below, I&amp;rsquo;ve included a couple of customer support requests I received recently, along with my responses. To protect customer privacy, I&amp;rsquo;ve redacted and changed details of the requests, while ensuring the core of the question remains the same.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data_viz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data_viz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;wikipedia-mathematicians-data-vis&#34;&gt;Wikipedia mathematicians data vis&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where to view this portfolio piece: &lt;a href=&#34;https://jackhiggins458.github.io/Wiki-Mathematicians/&#34;&gt;at this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I love communicating through writing, but some situations call for something more visual.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I graduated with a Bachelor of Science, majoring in both mathematics and computational science, including studies in algorithmics and data visualisation. My love of maths, data visualisation and Wikipedia bore this &amp;ldquo;Mathematicians of Wikipedia&amp;rdquo; visualisation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The inspiration for this page came from a collision of different interests at the time:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/methodology_report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/methodology_report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;exoporter-analysis-methodology-report&#34;&gt;Exoporter analysis methodology report&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where to view this portfolio piece: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.abs.gov.au/methodologies/characteristics-australian-exporters-methodology/2019-20&#34;&gt;on the Australian Bureau of Statistics website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While I used whatever leftover time I could find in my day to help create learning material for colleagues at the ABS (see my &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/nn_tutorial/&#34;&gt;Interactive neural networks tutorial&lt;/a&gt; piece), the bulk of my time was spent doing analysis and reporting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In one project, I was responsible for working with staff in the international trade team on developing and documenting a new methodology for analysing Australian exporters. While in this case &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.abs.gov.au/statistics/economy/international-trade/characteristics-australian-exporters/latest-release&#34;&gt;the actual analysis of the data was left to the international trade team&lt;/a&gt;, I delivered the associated methodology report, which the key concepts, methods and data sources used.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/nn_tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/nn_tutorial/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;interactive-neural-networks-tutorial&#34;&gt;Interactive neural networks tutorial&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where to view this portfolio piece: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jackhiggins458/Neural_Network_Tutorial/&#34;&gt;on GitHub (non-interactive)&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://mybinder.org/v2/gh/jackhiggins458/Neural_Network_Tutorial/HEAD?labpath=notebooks%2F0_Welcome.ipynb&#34;&gt;on Binder (interactive)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my first role after graduating university, I worked as a data analyst at Australia&amp;rsquo;s national statistical agency, the Australian Bureau of Statistics (ABS).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the ABS, I was involved in the machine learning community of practice (ML CoP). At the time, there was growing interest from staff in machine learning methods, as many were beginning to see use in statistical production processes. As a result, we had a large increase in new members to the community, many of whom didn&amp;rsquo;t have much of a background in machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
